PAULINE SULIT

FRONT-END DEVELOPER paulinesulit.com

PROFILE

I'm a front-end developer with 3+ years experience in the technology industry, currently in adtech and educated in International Development and Health Studies. My passion for learning and problem-solving evolved into developing responsive and accessible web applications.

PROJECTS

PAGE TURNERS

HTML / CSS / SCSS / React / Rest APIs / Firebase

 Worked in group programming creating an app that pulls the Google Books API, allowing a user to search for books, store them in a reading list and see their progress with how many books they've read

EXPERIENCE

Associate Solutions Engineer Blockthrough | Apr 2022 - Present

- · Review and test client implementations and troubleshoot issues using devtools
- Acts as primary liaison between Account Managers and Engineering teams to provide technical feedback and client-facing strategies

Microsoft Order Management Associate Softchoice | Nov 2020 - Oct 2021

- Audited salesforce quotes, processed and invoiced 50-70 Microsoft orders on a daily basis focusing on quality, accuracy, and speed through SAP and Microsoft portals
- Problem solved technical issues and rejection orders alongside cross-functional teams to determine the root of problems and provided the best course of action

Product Management Associate Softchoice | Jul 2019 - Oct 2020

- Results-oriented completing 15-30 product data requests via the Salesforce Case queue, and achieving/surpassing the goal of 92% SLA response rate on a regular basis
- Initiated the use of SQL and Excel alongside team members for mass product searches for efficiency









EDUCATION

Web Development, Immersive **Juno College of Technology** | Nov 2021 - Feb 2022

Honours Bachelor of Arts, Double Major in Health Studies and International Development **University of Toronto** | Sept 2014 - Jun 2018

TECH STACK







SCSS



JavaScript



iQuery



React

CSS





Firebase





SQL



Terminal



SKILLS

- Jira
- Confluence
- SAP
- Salesforce
- MS Excel, Word, PPT, Outlook, Teams
- G-Suite
- Paired / Mob Programming
- Teamwork / Collaboration
- Problem-solving
- Detail-oriented
- Time Management